Guide to the Franco Modigliani papers, 1936-2005 and undated, bulk 1970s-2003 RL.00905
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches Series, 1936-2004 and undated, 58 boxes
  - Research and Writings Subseries, 1936-2004 and undated, bulk 1960-2003, 44 boxes
    - Consumption and reduced form estimation
      - Reduced form tests, 1971 and undated (Box RW6)
    - Conventional Valuation and the Term Structure of Interest Rates, R. Shiller - Comment, F. Modigliani, 1986 (Conference on Martha's Vineyard) (Box RW6)
    - Convertibility and Consolidation, Peter Kenen - Notes, undated (Box RW6)
    - Convertible Bonds in Spain, F. Modigliani, circa 1985 (Box RW6)
    - The Cost of Capital, Corporate Finance and the Theory of Investment, with Merton Miller
      - Drafts, 1958 (Box RW6)
      - Notes and related papers, 1962 (Box RW6)
      - Notes, drafts, and related papers, 1958-1962 (Box RW6)
      - Related papers, 1963 (Box RW6)
    - Costs of Economic Progress, Malinvaud - Comments, F. Modigliani, 1977 (Box RW6)
    - Coupon and Tax Effects on New and Seasoned Bond Yields and the Measurement of the Cost of Debt Control, with Robert Shiller
      - Estimations and data, 1979 (Box RW6)
      - Notes and correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box RW6)
      - Related papers and drafts, 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box RW6)
    - Criticism of Monetary Policy in 1977, 1977 (Box RW6)
    - Currency, union stability, and fiscal policy - Notes, undated (Box RW6)
    - The Debt and the Deficit: False Alarms and Real Possibilities, R. Heilbroner and P. Bernstein - Review, F. Modigliani, 1989 (Box RW7)
    - Debt, Dividend Policy, Taxes, Inflation and Market Valuation, American Finance Association presidential address, 1981 Dec. 28-30
      - A Correction, 1982 May (Box RW7)
      - Drafts and notes, 1982 (Box RW7)
      - Notes, circa 1981 (Box RW7)
      - Printed materials, 1967-1982, 2 folders (Box RW7)
    - Determinants of Private Saving with Special Reference to the Role of Social Security, with A. Sterling, 1983 (Box RW7)
    - Determinants of Private Saving with Special Reference to the Role of Social Security - Cross Country Tests, with A. Sterling, 1981 Apr. (Box RW7)
    - Distribution of wealth and income, circa 1977 (Box RW7)
    - Dividend Decisions and Earnings, with P. Healy, 1988-1990 (Box RW7)
    - Econometric Analysis of Stabilization Policies, with A. Ando, 1968-1969 (Box RW7)
    - Econometric model - Research and printed material, 1965 (Box RW7)
    - Econometric model of the Bank of Italy - Notes, circa 1966 (Box RW7)
    - Econometric Models of Stabilization Policies, 1968 (Box RW7)
    - The Economics of Public Deficits - Notes and draft, 1984 (Box RW8)
    - The Economics of Science and Technology, with H. Jacoby, 1987 Apr. 4 (Box RW8)
    - An Economists' Manifesto on Unemployment in the European Union, with J-P. Fitoussi, F. Giavazzi, et al.
      - Correspondence, 1998 (Box RW8)
      - Correspondence and drafts, 1998, 2 folders (Box RW8)
      - Correspondence, contract, and drafts, 1998-2000 (Box RW8)
      - Correspondence with Jacques Drèze, 1997 (Box RW8)
      - Unemployment notes, 1994-1998 (Box RW8)
    - Effect of Fiscal Policy on Saving, with A. Mason and A. Sterling, 1984 (Box RW8)
    - Effects of Inflation on Valuation - Notes, 1979 Oct. (Box RW8)
    - The Effect of Taxes on Corporate Valuation, Summers, Feldstein, et al. - Criticism, F. Modigliani, 1980 Oct. (Box RW8)
    - Efficiency of the European Capital Markets and a Comparison with the American Market, with G. Pogue, M. Scholes, et al., 1972 and 1980, 2 folders (Box RW8)
    - Empirical Analysis of Composition of Financial Wealth in Italy, with F. Cotula, 1972-1973 (Box RW8)
    - Errata, undated (Box RW8)
    - Essence of Modigliani - Chinese translation of selected papers, 2001 (Box RW8)
    - Eurocurrencies and the Evolution of the International Monetary System, J. Makin - Comment, F. Modigliani, 1976 (Box RW9)
    - The European Unemployment Crisis: A Monetarist-Keynesian Approach and Its Implications
      - Correspondence
        - 1994-1995 (Box RW9)
        - French translation, 1995 (Box RW9)
        - Indian Journal of Applied Economics, 1995 (Box RW9)
        - Italian version, with M. Baldassarri, 1995 (Box RW9)
        - Spanish version, 1995 (Box RW9)
      - Drafts, circa 1994-1995, 3 folders (Box RW9)
      - Published manuscript, 1995 (Box RW9)
      - Working paper, 1994 Dec. (Box RW9)
    - European Union - Italian/German relations
      - Faxes, 1997 (Box RW9)
      - Research notes and printed material, 1993-1997 (Box RW9)
    - Exchange rate market - Notes, undated; printed material, 1983 (Box RW9)
    - Explaining the Administration's Economic Program, circa 1975 (Box RW9)
    - Fama, Eugene - Notes, undated (Box RW10)
    - FASB (Financial Accounting Standards Board) - AER ( American Economic Review) Committee on Statement #33
      - Correspondence, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box RW10)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1983-1985 (Box RW10)
      - Correspondence and printed material, 1984 (Box RW10)
      - Printed material, 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box RW10)
      - Report on Statement #33
        - Data tables, 1984 Nov. 5 (Box RW10)
        - Drafts and notes, circa 1985 (Box RW10)
        - Report, 1984-1985 (Box RW10)
        - Report requests, 1985 (Box RW10)
    - Federal budget deficit - Printed material, 1983-1986 (Box RW10)
    - Federal Reserve Bank ( Boston), 1988-2001 (Box RW11)
    - Federal Reserve Targets table, circa 1987 (Box RW11)
    - The Financial Goal of the Firm in a Market Economy - Draft and notes, 1978-1979 (Box RW11)
    - Financial markets - Book proposal with R. Cohn, circa 1982 (Box RW11)
    - Firm Cost Structures and the Dynamic Responses of Production, Work Force and Orders to Sales Fluctuations, with C. Holt, 1961 Oct. (Box RW11)
    - Fiscal Policy, Inflation and Private Saving: Evidence from an International Cross-Section, with A. Mason and A. Sterling, 1986 (Box RW11)
    - Fiscal Policy and Saving in Italy Since 1860, with T. Jappelli - Data, 1987 (Box RW11)
    - Foundations of Financial Markets and Institutions, with F. Fabozzi, M. Ferri, et al.
      - Chapters 11, 12, and 22, 1992-1993 (Box RW11)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1997; paper, 1992 (Box RW11)
    - FRB (Federal Reserve Board) - MPS (MIT-Penn.-Social Sciences Research Council) Model
      - Andersen, Lepnall, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box RW11)
      - Boston Federal Reserve Board, 1968 May 2 (Box RW11)
      - Central Bank Policy and the Money Supply, with R. Rasche, undated (Box RW12)
      - Chicago conference, 1968 Apr., 2 folders (Box RW12)
      - Consumption notes - FRB, 1968 (Box RW12)
      - Cowles conference, 1968 Sept. 20-21 (Box RW12)
      - The DHL-III Quarterly Econometric Model of the U.S. Economy, S. Hymans and H. Shapiro, 1969 Oct. (Box RW12)
      - Econometric Analysis of Stabilization Policies, with A. Ando
        - Christmas - Japan, 1968-1969 (Box RW12)
        - 1968 (Box RW12)
      - Employment Equations
        - Composition effects, 1968-1969 (Box RW12)
        - 1968-1969 (Box RW12)
      - EPA World Economic Model, Japan, 1991, 2 folders (Box RW12)
      - Federal model, MPS, and extrapolation, 1970-1972, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box RW12)
      - Federal model, MPS, and extrapolation, 1970-1972, Folder 3 of 3 (Box RW13)
      - Financial markets, 1969, 2 folders (Box RW13)
      - FMP (Federal Reserve Board-MIT-Penn.)
        - Housing sector, circa 1970, 2 folders (Box RW13)
        - Miscellaneous sector, undated (Box RW13)
        - Monograph - Consumption sector, 1970-1971 (Box RW13)
      - FRB - Memos, 1968 (Box RW13)
      - Investment and inventories, circa 1970 (Box RW13)
      - The Lag Between Orders and Production of Machinery and Equipment: A Reexamination of the Kareken-Solow Results, C. Bischoll, 1968 July (Box RW14)
      - Material for monograph, 1970 (Box RW14)
      - Meetings of the subcommittee on monetary research, 1969 May 2 (Box RW14)
      - Model extrapolations, 1971 (Box RW14)
      - Monetary and Fiscal Influences on Economic Activity: The Historical Evidence, M. Keran, 1969 (Box RW14)
      - Money market, 1969 (Box RW14)
      - MPS
        - Database, undated, 2 folders (Box RW14)
        - Model
          - 1972-circa 1975, 3 folders (Box RW14)
        - Monograph - Foundations financial sector, 1969-1973 (Box RW14)
      - Notebook, 1968-1969, 4 folders (Box RW15)
      - Notes and econometric estimations, 1972-1973 (Box RW15)
      - Notes, undated, and papers 1967-1968 (Box RW15)
      - Outline of book, 1975 (Box RW15)
      - Print out of Kourmandi's data and other estimation outputs, undated, 2 folders (Box RW15)
      - The Quarterly Econometric Model
        - 1977, 2 folders (Box RW15)
        - 1978 (Box RW16)
        - 1983 (Box RW16)
      - The Quarterly Econometric Model Data Directory
        - 1975 (Box RW16)
        - 1980, 2 folders (Box RW16)
      - The Quarterly Econometric Model Equations, 1973 (Box RW16)
      - Report on FRB-MIT model, 1970, 2 folders (Box RW16)
      - Revisions, 1963 (Box RW16)
      - The SIM Model Solution Program, M. Norman, H. Shapiro, and R. Rasche, circa 1968 (Box RW16)
      - Simulations, 1971, 3 folders (Box RW16)
      - Simulations code, 1971, 2 folders (Box RW17)
      - The Structure of the Model, with A. Ando and F. de Leeuw, 1966-1967 (Box RW17)
      - Term structure - RCB - NFS, 1970, 2 folders (Box RW17)
      - Wage-Labor force participation, 1971 (Box RW17)
      - Wage-Price dynamics, 1968-1971 (Box RW17)
    - La funzione del partito nel controllo dei prezzi, undated (Box RW17)
    - Generalization of Phillip's Curve for a Developing Country, with E. Tarantelli, 1971-1973 (Box RW17)
    - The General Theory of Employment Interest and Money Under the Assumptions of Flexible Prices and of Fixed Prices, 1944 (Box RW17)
      [Modigliani's doctoral thesis; photocopy from original held by New York City's New School of Social Research. Missing pp. 81-99.]
    - Goss, Stephen, 2000 (Box RW17)
    - Government Debt, Government Spending, and Private Sector Behavior: Comment, with A. Sterling (Box RW18)
      - Correspondence, notes and drafts, 1985-1990 and undated, 2 folders (Box RW18)
      - Papers and printed material, 1968-1987 (Box RW18)
    - The Growth of the Federal Deficit and the Role of Public Attitudes, with A. Modigliani
      - Correspondence and notes, circa 1936; printed material, 1939-1987 (Box RW18)
      - Data, circa 1986 (Box RW18)
      - Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box RW18)
      - Italian translation, 1987 (Box RW18)
    - Has the Economist Lost Control of the Economy? 1979 (Box RW18)
    - Herbert Simon: Some Cherished Memories, 2003 (published 2004 May) (Box RW18)
    - Impacts of Fiscal Actions on Aggregate Income and the Monetarist..., with A. Ando, 1976 (Box RW18)
    - The Impact of Fiscal Policy and Inflation on National Saving, with T. Jappelli and M. Pagano, 1984-1985 and undated, Folder 1 of 2 (Box RW18)
    - The Impact of Fiscal Policy and Inflation on National Saving, with T. Jappelli and M. Pagano, 1984-1985 and undated, Folder 2 of 2 (Box RW19)
    - L'impatto della politica fiscale e dell'inflazione sul risparmio nazionale: un commento, with T. Jappelli and M. Pagano, 1989 (Box RW19)
    - Improving the Monetary Aggregates, Report of the Advisory Committee on Monetary Statistics, 1976 (Box RW19)
    - In Europa il futuro pensionistico delle casse professionali, with M. Ceprini, 2003 (Box RW19)
    - The Inefficiency of Short-Run Monetary Targets for Monetary Policy, B. Friedman - Comment, F. Modigliani, 1980 (Box RW19)
    - Inflation
      - Inflation and Corporate Financial Management, with R. Cohn - Correspondence, drafts, and working paper, 1983-1984 (Box RW19)
      - Inflation and Finance - Correspondence and draft, 1989 (Box RW19)
      - Inflation, Financial and Fiscal Structure, and the Monetary Mechanism, with L. Papademos - Correspondence and notes, 1982-1983 (Box RW19)
      - Inflation and the Housing Market..., with D. Lessard, 1975-1980 (Box RW19)
      - Inflation, indexed bonds and equity swaps - Notes, circa 2000 (Box RW19)
      - Inflation-Induced Distortions in Financial Reporting and Taxation, 1979-1981 (Box RW19)
      - The Inflation-Proof Mortgage..., 1984-1989, 2 folders (Box RW19)
      - Inflation, Rational Valuation and the Market, with R. Cohen
        - 1979 (Box RW19)
        - Business Week and Newsweek comments, 1980 (Box RW19)
        - Fortune article, 1979 Mar. 12; Financial Analysts Journal article, 1986 Sept.-Oct. (Box RW19)
        - Original notes and figures, 1979 (Box RW19)
      - Inflation and the Stock Market, with R. Cohn (Box RW20)
        - Correspondence, 1979, 2 folders (Box RW20)
        - Correspondence and draft, 1980-1981; printed material, 1981 (Box RW20)
    - Innovations in Interest Rate Policy, with R. Sutch - Correspondence and drafts, 1965-1997 (Box RW20)
    - Innovations in Interest Rate Policy..., F. Steindl and D. De La Torre Ungarte - Reply, F. Modigliani and R. Shiller, 1989 Dec. (Box RW20)
    - Intergenerational accounting
      - Notes and correspondence, 1987 and undated (Box RW20)
      - Printed material, 1985-1995 (Box RW20)
    - International Capital Movement, Fixed Parities, and Monetary and Fiscal Policies
      - Correspondence and drafts, 1965-1966 (Box RW20)
      - Draft, undated (Box RW20)
    - International Payment System: Past, Present, and Future, with H. Askari
      - 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box RW20)
      - Correspondence and notes, 1971-1972; printed material, 1966-1972 (Box RW20)
      - Printed material, 1969-1972 (Box RW20)
    - International Transfer of Capital..., with H. Askari, circa 1973 (Box RW21)
    - An Introduction to Risk and Return Concepts and Evidence, with G. Pogue, 1973-1987 (Box RW21)
    - Investments vs. Savings Incentives..., A. Auerbach and L. Kotlikoff - Comment, F. Modigliani, 1982 Oct. (Box RW21)
    - Is Senator Moynihan All Wrong or All Right? circa 1990, 2 folders (Box RW21)
    - The Italian Economic Crisis: Causes, Cures and Some Political Implications, 1975-1976 (Box RW21)
    - Italian economy
      - Notes and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box RW21)
      - Notes and reports (Confindustria and others), 1993-1994 and undated (Box RW21)
    - Italian labor market - Proposed book with E. Tarantelli, 1979 (Box RW21)
    - Italy - Notes and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box RW21)
    - Italy: Past Experience with Deindexation, 1983-1984 (published 1985) (Box RW21)
    - Jappelli, Tullio - Notes, correspondence and drafts, 1994-2002 and undated, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box RW21)
    - Jappelli, Tullio - Notes, correspondence and drafts, 1994-2002 and undated, Folder 3 of 3 (Box RW22)
    - Keynes - Modigliani's autobiography, undated (Box RW22)
    - The Keynesian Gospel According to Modigliani
      - Correspondence and notes, 2001-2003 and undated (Box RW22)
      - Drafts, 2001-2003 (Box RW22)
      - Notes and correspondence, 1999-2003 and undated (Box RW22)
      - Printed material, 1936-2003 (Box RW22)
    - Lessons Learned from Barbara, [ex-student, then colleague] 1996-1997 (published 1998) (Box RW22)
    - Life cycle hypothesis
      - Life Cycle Hypothesis - In the New Palgrave Dictionary of Money and Finance
        - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box RW22)
        - Drafts and proofs, 1991 (Box RW22)
        - Papers, 1991 (Box RW22)
      - Life cycle hypothesis - Printed material, 1980-1982; note, circa 1981 (Box RW22)
      - Life cycle hypothesis and consumption function
        - Consumer surveys, 1964-1982, Folder 1 of 2 (Box RW22)
        - Consumer surveys, 1964-1982, Folder 2 of 2 (Box RW23)
        - International comparison
          - Econometric estimation (Box RW23)
          - I, circa 1964, 2 folders (Box RW23)
          - II, undated, 3 folders (Box RW23)
          - III, undated (Box RW23)
        - Notes, bibliographic material, and obsolete estimations, undated (Box RW23)
        - With A. Fazio
          - Basic data and notes, circa 1964 (Box RW23)
          - Data and notes, undated (Box RW23)
          - Data and regressions, undated (Box RW23)
          - Notes and drafts, circa 1962 (Box RW24)
          - Memos and summaries, 1962-1963 and undated (Box RW24)
          - Regressions and tests, 1962 (Box RW24)
        - LCH tests - Data and paper, circa 1983 (Box RW24)
        - Life cycle wealth and bequest motives - Notes on L. Kotlikoff and L. Summers, et al., undated, 2 folders (Box RW24)
        - Papers, 1969-1983 and undated, Folders 1-4 of 6 folders (Box RW24)
        - Papers, 1969-1983 and undated, Folders 5-6 of 6 folders (Box RW25)
        - Printed material, 1979-2002, 3 folders (Box RW25)
        - Recent Declines in the Savings Rate..., 1990 (Box RW25)
        - Saving Trends and Behaviour in OECD Countries, A. Dean, M. Durand, et al., 1989 (Box RW25)
        - Wealth - National debt - Capital coefficient - Econometric estimations, undated (Box RW25)
      - Life Cycle Hypothesis and National Wealth, L. Kotlikoff and L. Summers - Comments, F. Modigliani, 1983 (Box RW25)
      - The Life Cycle Hypothesis of Saving and the Effect of Investment on Economic Growth, with M. Gibson
        - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box RW25)
        - Printed material, 1991-1996 (Box RW25)
        - Research notes, 1992-1995 and undated (Box RW25)
      - Life Cycle Hypothesis of Saving, Demand for Wealth, and Supply of Capital (Box RW26)
        - Original draft, 1965 (Box RW26)
        - Printed material with notes, 1958-1963 (Box RW26)
        - Tests of Long Run Determinants of Saving Ratio Based on International Comparisons - Chapter III, 1965 (Box RW26)
      - Life-Cycle Hypothesis: Theory and Evidence, T. Juster, 1987 (Box RW26)
      - Life Cycle, Individual Thrift, and the Wealth of Nations, 1986 (Box RW26)
    - Liquidity Preference, in The International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences
      - Drafts, circa 1968 (Box RW26)
      - Notes and correspondence, circa 1965, 2 folders (Box RW26)
      - Papers, 1964-circa 1965 and undated, 2 folders (Box RW26)
    - Long Term Financing in an Inflationary Environment, 1992 (Box RW26)
    - Management of an Open Economy..., with T. Padoa-Schioppa, 1978 (Box RW26)
    - Managing Oil-Type Problems Through Taxation, 1979 Dec. (Box RW26)
    - Market timing newsletters, 1994-1997 (Box RW26)
    - Massachusetts model of profit regulation and nonlife insurance - R. Hill, 1981 Apr. (Box RW26)
    - Matrix of claims and markets - U.S., 1965 (Box RW26)
    - Misguided Monetary Policy Bears the Main Responsibility for European Unemployment, with M. Ceprini, 2000 (Box RW26)
    - (Frederic?) Mishkin - Comments, F. Modigliani, 1978 (Box RW26)
    - MIT economic and finance group - Problems of housing and thrift institutions - Letter to Frank Raines, 1977 Apr. 12 (Box RW26)
    - Models of the Economy and Optimal Stabilization Policies
      - Appendix A, 1976 (Box RW26)
      - Appendix B, 1976 (Box RW26)
      - Russian paper
        - Draft, 1976 (Box RW26)
        - Notes, 1976 (Box RW27)
    - Modigliani, Leah, 1997 (Box RW27)
    - M-M - Past, Present, and Future
      - Copyrights, 1988 (Box RW27)
      - Draft, undated; correspondence, 1988 (Box RW27)
      - Early drafts, 1988 (Box RW27)
      - References, 1988 (Box RW27)
      - Reprint and notes, 1988 (Box RW27)
      - Various drafts and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box RW27)
      - Various papers and notes, 1958-1987, 2 folders (Box RW27)
    - Monetarism - Printed material, 1966-1969; paper, undated (Box RW27)
    - Monetarist Controversy, or Should We Forsake Stabilization Policies, AEA presidential address - Correspondence and research notes, 1976-1990, 2 folders (Box RW27)
    - The Monetarist Controversy Revisited, 1988 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary Mechanism and Its Interaction with Real Phenomena, 1963 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary Mechanism and Stabilization Policy, with L. Papademos
      - NSF research proposal, 1979 (Box RW27)
      - NSF research notes and correspondence, 1979 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary Policy for 1975, 1975 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary Policy and Consumption...
      - Correspondence and notes, 1971-1974 and undated (Box RW27)
      - NSF proposal, 1972 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary Policy for Coming Quarters, with L. Papademos, 1976 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary policy and price rigidity - Notes, circa 1970 (Box RW27)
    - Monetary theory - Notes on Hahn and other materials, undated, 2 folders (Box RW28)
    - Money, Credit and the Monetary Mechanism, with L. Papademos, 1987 (Box RW28)
    - Money supply mechanism, undated (Box RW28)
    - Money, Wealth, Growth and Fluctuations, undated (Box RW28)
    - Mortgages
      - Alternative Mortgage Instruments for Affordable Homeownership
        - 1990 Dec. 4 (Box RW28)
        - 1991 Feb. 15 (Box RW28)
      - Canada, 1986 (Box RW28)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1990, 4 folders (Box RW28)
      - France - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box RW28)
      - French and Mexican mortgage chapter, 1992 (Box RW28)
      - Hungary, 1991 (Box RW28)
      - Inflation and housing - Correspondence and drafts, 1984-1991; printed material, 1975-1990 (Box RW28)
      - Inflation and the Housing Market: Problems and Potential Solutions, with D. Lessard, 1975 (Box RW28)
      - Italy - Correspondence, notes, and data tables, 1984-1988 and undated (Box RW28)
      - Mexico, 1984-1991 and undated, 2 folders (Box RW28)
      - MIT Flexible Graduated Payment Mortgage (Box RW29)
        - Copyright, 1984 (Box RW29)
        - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box RW29)
        - Extra tables, circa 1987 (Box RW29)
        - The French Connection, 1990 (Box RW29)
      - MIT mailing list, circa 1985 (Box RW29)
      - The MOD Card, 1988-1989 (Box RW29)
      - Modigliani, Sergio, 1988-1990 (Box RW29)
      - Mortgage Design and Affordable Homeownership, with D. DiPasquale, 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box RW29)
      - Mortgages and Mortgage Backed Securities, with F. Fabozzi, 1992 (Box RW29)
      - Mortgages, security markets, and inflation indexed bonds
        - Printed material, 1978-1989 (Box RW29)
        - Research notes, 1971-1984 and undated, 2 folders (Box RW29)
      - Mortgage study report
        - HUD conference handouts, 1975 (Box RW29)
        - Inflation and the Housing Market, with D. Lessard, 1975 Oct. (Box RW30)
        - Macroeconomic Simulations of Alternative Mortgage Instruments, D. Jaffee and J. Kearl, circa 1975 (Box RW30)
        - Newspaper articles, 1975 (Box RW30)
        - Report #1 - Some Implications of Indexing of Financial Assets..., 1974 Sept. (Box RW30)
        - Report #2 - The Sloan School Mortgage Study..., 1974 Oct. (Box RW30)
        - Report #3 - Relationships Between the Mortgage Instrument..., J. Kearl, K. Rosen, et al., 1974 Nov. (Box RW30)
        - Report #4 - Tax Aspects of Alternative Mortgage Instruments, D. Holland, 1974 Dec. (Box RW30)
        - Report #5 - An Analysis of Alternative Nonstandard Mortgages, R. Cohn and S. Fischer, 1974 Dec. (Box RW30)
        - Task II - An Analysis of Alternative Nonstandard Mortgages, R. Cohn and S. Fischer, circa 1974 (Box RW30)
        - Task III - Appendix to the Financial Determinants..., J. Kearl, K. Rosen, et al., 1975 (Box RW30)
        - Task IV
          - Roll-Over Mortgages in China, D. Lessard, 1974 Dec. (Box RW30)
          - Financing of Housing in Finland..., P. Kouri, circa 1974 (Box RW30)
          - Experience with Variable Rate Mortgages..., D. Cohen and D. Lessard, 1974 Dec. (Box RW30)
          - Index-Linked Mortgages in Israel, Alex Cukerman, 1975 Feb. (Box RW30)
          - Mortgage Innovation to Facilitate Investment in Housing..., D. Cohen and D. Lessard, circa 1975 (Box RW30)
        - Task V - Interim Report for Task V, with D. Jaffee, J. Kearl, et al., circa 1975 (earlier version) (Box RW30)